<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CareerOpportunities_menu>

<CareerOpportunities>
<name> Business development manager</name>
<vac> vacancies-3</vac>
<description>BuzzIT! is a digital agency based in New Delhi, India. We specialise in creating digital marketing solutions for web, mobile and social media to help companies engage and inspire their audiences.We are still a young agency, with a strong portfolio comprised of several high profile brands in India and Abroad. We are a small team of skilled and friendly people, very passionate about our work and committed to constantly delivering a top quality service for which we are valued by our clients.</description>
<expected_sla_pa>5-7 lpa</expected_sla_pa>
</CareerOpportunities>

<CareerOpportunities>
<name>Content writer</name>
<vac> vacancies-3</vac>
<description>Work involves writing original English Language content for websites after sound research on given topics. Ability to compose grammatically correct sentences and paragraphs that combine factual information presented in an engaging manner.</description>
<expected_sla_pa>5-7 lpa</expected_sla_pa>
</CareerOpportunities>

<CareerOpportunities>
<name>SEO expert</name>
<vac> vacancies-3</vac>
<description> This role involves managing a portfolio of clients and improving their search engine optimization by using techniques including but not exclusive to: Keyword Research, Copy Optimization, Article Marketing, site structure, URL re‐writes, social media, blogging and link building. An understanding of Paid search marketing would be advantageous.</description>
<expected_sla_pa>4-5 lpa</expected_sla_pa>
</CareerOpportunities>

<CareerOpportunities>
<name>Pay Per Click expert</name>
<vac> vacancies-3</vac>
<description>Monitoring and Analysis of PPC campaigns of various Clients.Tracking and analysis of traffic metrics for all channels using Google Analytics and similar web analytic tools.</description>
<expected_sla_pa>4-5 lpa</expected_sla_pa>
</CareerOpportunities>

<CareerOpportunities>
<name>Social media stragist</name>
<vac> vacancies-3</vac>
<description>Monitoring and Analysis of PPC campaigns of various Clients.Tracking and analysis of traffic metrics for all channels using Google Analytics and similar web analytic tools.</description>
<expected_sla_pa>5-7 lpa</expected_sla_pa>
</CareerOpportunities>

<CareerOpportunities>
<name>Digital Media Stratigist</name>
<vac> vacancies-3</vac>
<description>BuzzIT!, a digital marketing company in New Delhi is looking for a Digital marketing analyst who will be responsible for working with a portfolio of clients to assist in: defining and implementing measurement strategies that align with clients’ marketing and business objectives, producing meaningful marketing KPI dashboards and delivering monthly, cross channel performance reports with actionable insight. The role will also involve conducting conversion and  optimization consulting, with the aim of improving efficiency in clients’ digital marketing strategies and increase in ROI.</description>
<expected_sla_pa>6-9 lpa</expected_sla_pa>
</CareerOpportunities>

</CareerOpportunities_menu> 